<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SpeedStormApp</string>

    <string name="name">Fayshal Karan Athilla</string>
    <string name="email">fayshalkaranathilla12@student.cs.unida.gontor.ac.id</string>
    <string name="racer_name">Racer Name</string>
    <string name="racer_description">Description</string>
    <string name="list">List</string>
    <string name="grid">Grid</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
    <string name="language_name">Nama Program</string>
    <string name="user_name">Adam Toyib Nurwahid</string>
    <string name="user_email">fayshalkaranathilla12@student.cs.unida.gontor.ac.id</string>
    <string name="email_pengguna">fayshalkaranathilla12@student.cs.unida.gontor.ac.id</string>
    <string name="nama_pengguna">Fayshal Karan Athilla</string>


    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>WALL-E</item>
        <item>BALOO</item>
        <item>STEAMBOAT MICKEY</item>
        <item>BELLE</item>
        <item>DAVY JONES</item>
        <item>SULLEY</item>
        <item>BUZZ LIGTHYEAR</item>
        <item>STICTH</item>
        <item>ELSA</item>
        <item>JOY</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>WALL-E is a waste-collector drone in the world of the future. Unlike other racers, WALL-E does not wear a racing suit, and instead keeps a similar appearance to the original Disney film, but with a brighter orange paint job to give him a brand-new look and with slight additional patterns to enhance the racing driver image. His Unique ability allows him to use piles of garbage as a source of extra speed, as well as a powerful fire extinguisher that pushes him forwards.</item>
        <item>Baloo is a big dark-gray sloth bear. His belly, claws and snout stand out being a lighter shade of gray. In Disney Speedstorm, Baloo\’s racing suit resembles his original Disney look: it mostly blends in with his fur color but has a lighter oval part on his belly, and there are some green inserts that are associated with his natural habitat — the jungle. Baloo\’s personality in the game was also inspired by his original movie prototype: he is a fun-loving smiley bear who loves everyone around him even while trying to win. His Unique ability lets other Racers pick up fruits on the road to speed them up.</item>
        <item>Steamboat Mickey is the retro version of Mickey Mouse that appeared in the black and white cartoon "Steamboat Willie". The design of Steamboat Mickey in Disney Speedstorm mostly resembles his original Disney prototype: he is a black and white mouse wearing a racing suit of the same color and a captain cap. His personality is similar to Mickey Mouse: cheerful, playful and positive. Steamboat Mickey\’s unique ability adds a helm of his boat to his car which makes him look authentic.</item>
        <item>Belle is a village girl whose fate changes when her father is imprisoned by the Beast. In Disney Speedstorm, Belle\’s yellow dress from the finale of the original Disney movie has been transformed into her banana color driving suit. Her personality in the game also resembles her film prototype: she is cheerful, romantic and passionate about winning. She either uses the Enchanted Mirror to summon magic furniture on her opponents way making them bump into it and lose advantage, or she summons magical birds to speed her up.</item>
        <item>Davy Jones is the captain of the Flying Dutchman. In Disney Speedstorm, Davy Jones\’s racing suit is heavily inspired by his original movie outfit: it is a dark-navy suit with cuffed sleeves and marsh colored shins and shoulders. True to the original, he has a peg leg that resembles a crab, as well as a crab claw for his left arm, and long tentacles that are meant to serve as a beard have been preserved in the game. He also wears his iconic pirate hat.</item>
        <item>Sulley is a big and scary cat-looking monster. In Disney Speedstorm, his blue racing suit with white and dark-gray stripes is inspired by the color palette of his jacket from the second movie, but it is mostly an original outfit due to Sulley not wearing any clothes most of the time. His personality in the game was also inspired by his film prototype: he is amiable on the Racer select screen waving awkwardly without making eye contact, however, his Unique Skill is pure monster rage that is able to scare and stun his adversaries.</item>
        <item>Buzz is a new toy that joins Andy\’s collection in the beginning of the story. In Disney Speedstorm, his racing suit is extremely similar to his outfit in the original Pixar animated film: it is fully white with green and purple lines on his boots, trousers, top and sleeves, however, purple is a more predominant color than it was in the original. Buzz also wears his famous purple head cap and collar. His Unique ability is inspired by his pre-made backstory: as a space ranger he users rockets, which is how he can speed himself up during races or stun opponents behind and in front of him.</item>
        <item>Stitch is an alien experiment created by Jumba. In Disney Speedstorm, his red racing suit design is inspired by his original costume that he was wearing while being trapped on his home planet. His demeanor on the Racer select screen is also based on his original personality that he demonstrated while not being angry: he either jumps and smiles in a friendly way with all his sharp teeth being seen, or he awkwardly covers his eyes with his paws. Stitch\’s official announcement was on June 26, 2023, also known as "626 Day" or "Stitch Day" in reference to his original name "Experiment 626", which also became the name of his Unique ability that allows him to shoot his opponents with laser guns.</item>
        <item>Elsa is the queen of Arendelle and the Snow Queen of her own magic castle. In Disney Speedstorm, Elsa\’s white and cyan racing suit with light blue accents on the shoulders, sleeves and pants is inspired by the dress she was wearing in the original Disney film. Her iconic hairstyle has also been preserved in the game, and her animation on the Racing select screen includes arm movements similar to the ones she made when she got changed into her new outfit. Her Unique ability is pure ice magic: she freezes opponents in front of her or creates an ice wall behind her to stop others from catching up.</item>
        <item>•	Joy is one of the first and most basic emotions that appear in someone\’s head. In Disney Speedstorm, Joy\’s outfit is inspired by the dark yellow/lime dress she was wearing in the original Disney film: it is a banana-colored racing suit with blue stars all over it, white sleeves and calves, and light blue and white shoes. Joy\’s hairstyle and non-fading smile have been preserved in the game. As she is in charge of Riley\’s memories, Joy can speed herself up using her Unique ability and spawning lots of memory orbs that start rolling around the road.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/wall_e</item>
        <item>@drawable/baloo</item>
        <item>@drawable/steamboat_mickey</item>
        <item>@drawable/belle</item>
        <item>@drawable/davy_jones</item>
        <item>@drawable/sulley</item>
        <item>@drawable/buzz_lightyear</item>
        <item>@drawable/stitch</item>
        <item>@drawable/elsa</item>
        <item>@drawable/joy</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>